ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Files /4257
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Files
1963-1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4257
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
6181376
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
D. Mordente, February 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3019: ILR School Metropolitan District Selected Documents /4068: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office, Anne Nelson Papers /4089: ILR School Metropolitan District Office Additional Files /4266m: ILR School Metropolitan District Levi Strauss files /4277: ILR School Metropolitan District Trade Union Health Education Project Papers /4026: ILR School Metropolitan Office Extension Division Completed Questionnaires on Union Activity /4268: ILR School Metropolitan Office Records /4296: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Manuals /4296 AV: ILR School Extension Division Metropolitan District Office (New York, N.Y.) Training Audio-Visual Materials
Flight attendants -- Labor unions --New York (State); Women labor union members -- New York (State); Transport workers -- Labor unions -- New York (State); Home labor --New York (State); New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Metropolitan District Office.; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.); New York (N.Y.). City Commission on Human Rights; New York (N.Y.). Office of Labor Relations.
6181376
- Labor Unions- Flight Attendance, Transport Workers, 1976-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Labor Unions- Flight Attendance, 1963-1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Bibliography of Women Labor Leaders, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- NYC Commission on Human Rights & NYC Office of Labor Services: Public Hearing on the Construction Industry in NYC Folder 1, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- NYC Commission on Human Rights & NYC Office of Labor Services: Public Hearing on the Construction Industry in NYC Folder 2, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- NYC Commission on Human Rights & NYC Office of Labor Services: Public Hearing on the Construction Industry in NYC Copy 2, Folder 1, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- NYC Commission on Human Rights & NYC Office of Labor Services: Public Hearing on the Construction Industry in NYC Copy 2, Folder 2, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- CLUW- Articles about the CLUW, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- CLUW- Background & History, 1974-1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- CLUW- Articles & Speeches, 1972-1979 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- CLUW- (internal) Controversial Issues, 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Notes from the Planning Committee for a NYC Conference on Trade Union Women, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Women- Household Workers, 1969-1982 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Resolution for the NYC Federation of Labor Convention, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Labor Union Worker- UAW Women, 1967-1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- A Planning Manual for Coordinators of the University & College Labor Education Association's Northeast Summer School for Union Women & supplementary materials- Folder 1, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- A Planning Manual for Coordinators of the University & College Labor Education Association's Northeast Summer School for Union Women & supplementary materials- Folder 2, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ILR Credit and Certificate Program. Nash, Al., 1971-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- ILR Credit and Certificate Program. Nash, Al., 1975-1980 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Merger Documents., 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Voices Opposed to Merger., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- History of Merger Years., 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Teacher Unity. NYSUT/AFT., 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Harrison Report., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Strikes and Chapter 6., 1968-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Committee for NYSUT., 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)